selly.gg 2019-03-29

# Selly - Privacy Policy

### The Short Version

We collect your information only with your consent, we only collect the minimum amount of personal information that is necessary for us to fulfill our services for you. We don't sell any of your information to third parties.

This short version does not tell you everything, please continue reading for the full details

### Introduction

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. We also use cookies, a text fle stored on your browser, to help provide our Services. Our usage of cookies can be found outlined in our Cookies Policy .

### Applicability of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all websites that we own and operate, including the websites located at [selly.gg](https://selly.gg/) and all related websites, our applications and/or APIs, and online services (our “Site”), as well as our other services, offerings, and other interactions (e.g., customer service inquiries) you may have with us (together with our Site, collectively referred to as our “Services”). If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party applications or software that integrate with the Services through our Site (“Third Party Services”), or any other third party products, services or businesses

### Definitions

"Visitor" 

is someone who browses our Website, but has not registered as a Member. 

"Content" or "Goods" 

is all text, information, graphics, audio, video, products and data served via our Website or Service. 

"Member" 

is an individual that has registered to use our Service. 

"Merchant" or "Seller" 

is a Member that has registered with us to use our Payments or E-commerce Services and other applicable services. 

"Service" 

represents the collective functionality and features as offered through our Website to our terms. 

"User" 

is a collective identifier that refers to either a Visitor or a Member. 

"Customer" 

is a User that purchases or receives Goods, communicates with a Merchant, or engages in a payment via our Services. 

### Information We collect

**(a) Information you voluntarily provide to us:**

When you sign up for and use our Services, consult with our support team, send us an email, complete a form (for example the checkout form), integrate the Services with another website or service (for example, when you connect third party accounts with Selly), or communicate with us, you are voluntarily giving us information we collect. This information may include your email address, IP address, physical address, payment gateway information (for example, PayPal email, last 4 digits of your credit/debit card). By giving Selly this information, you consent to this information being collected and used by Selly.

**(b) Information we collect automatically:**

When you use our Services or browse our Websites, we may collect information about your usage of the Services and browsing of the Websites. This information may include, your IP address, operating system, browser, referral URL and other information about how you interacted with our Websites. We may collect this information as a part of log files as well as through the use of cookies.

**(d) Information from your use of a Service:**

When you use our Services or browse our Websites, we may collect information about your usage of the Service(s) and browsing of the Websites. This information may include, your IP address, operating system, browser, referral URL and other information about how you interacted with our Websites. We may collect this information as a part of log files as well as through the use of cookies.

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

**(a) To provide, support and improve upon the Services we offer:**

This may include our use of the data that our Members provide us in order to enable the Services to function and allow communication between Members and their customers. This may also include providing support for the Services from our support team.

**(b) To enforce compliance with our Terms of Service and applicable law:**

This may include developing algorithms and tools that help enforce compliance and detect violations.

**(c) To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.** **(d) To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.** **(e) To provide to Members as part of our Service:**

Members using our service will have access limited access to Personal Information of their Customers who have contacted or purchased from them. This Personal Information may include your IP address, browser, operating system and email address.

**(f) To transfer your information:**

In the case of a sale, merger, liquidation, acquisition, reorganization or consolidation, we may transfer your information. Any acquirer will be subject to our privacy policy. We will notify you of the change either by sending you an email or posting an announcement on our website.

**(g) To meet legal requirements:**

This may include complying with court orders, subpoenas and other legal mechanisms.

### Data Collected for and by our Members/Users

As part of our Services, we may use and incorporate into features, information you have provided, we have collected from you, or we have collected about Customers.

If you are a Customer and no longer want the Merchant to have access to the Personal information you previously gave consent for, contact us and we may be able to remove or update your information within a reasonable time after providing notice to the Merchant of your request.

We will retain Personal Information we process on behalf of our Members for as long as needed to provide our Services or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

**Your Rights**

European data protection laws give you certain rights regarding your personal information. You may ask us to take the following actions in relation to your personal information that we hold:

  * **Opt-out.** Stop sending you direct marketing communications. You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.
  * **Access.** Provide you with information about our processing of your personal information and give you access to your personal information.
  * **Correct.** Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
  * **Delete.** Delete your personal information.
  * **Transfer.** Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal information to you or a third party of your choice.
  * **Restrict.** Restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * **Object.** Object to our reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis of our processing of your personal information that impacts your rights.

You can submit these requests by email to at [legal@selly.gg](mailto:legal@selly.gg). We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our use of your personal information or response to your requests regarding your personal information, you may contact us at [legal@selly.gg](mailto:legal@selly.gg) or submit a complaint to the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction.

### Selly as a Data Processor

We may collect, use and disclose certain Personal Data about Customers when acting as the User’s service provider. Our Users are responsible for making sure that the Customer’s privacy rights are respected, including ensuring appropriate disclosures about third party data collection and use. To the extent that we are acting as a User’s data processor, we will process Personal Data in accordance with the terms of our agreement with the User and the User’s lawful instructions.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Selly's systems are scanned daily for any possible security holes to ensure your visit is safe as possible. Our backups are encrypted and stored in a secure isolated, offline manner. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential as well as the seller you purchased from or contacted. In addition, all requests to and from Selly are encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We acknowledge that the information you provide may be confidential and will maintain the confidentiality of and protect your information in accordance with our normal procedures and all applicable laws. We employ appropriate technical and organisational security measures to help protect your personal data against loss and to guard against access by unauthorised persons. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data security breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected breach where we are legally required to do so.

In addition, those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who process your personal data will only do so on our instructions and they will be subject to a duty of confidentiality.

### How can you access and control the information we collect?

If you're already a Selly User, you may access, update and alter your basic user information in your settings

Selly will retain User Personal Information for as long as needed to provide you and any relevant Users with services.

We may retain certain User Personal Information indefinitely unless you request its deletion. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, provide basic Services to our Users, and enforce our agreements, but barring legal requirements, on the request of deletion, Selly will delete your full user account (within reason) within 30 days.

### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google Analytics on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

  1. Impression Reporting
  2. Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### Changes to our Privacy Notice

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add to, or remove portions from, our Privacy Notice. We will of course notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.

Last updated: May 24th, 2018.

If you have any questions, please contact support. [contact@selly.gg](mailto:contact@selly.gg)
